# Chukwudumebi Obuaya

Lagos, Nigeria(GMT+1) | chukwudumebiobuaya@gmail.com | +234 7063529084 | www.linkedin.com/in/chukwudumebi-obuaya | https://github.com/dee-obuaya

## **Professional Summary**

With a little over a year of working experience, I have developed and built my skills not only in web development but also a little in networking, as well as in communicating and relating with others. I keep myself constantly open to learning, growing and new challenges. I have had the privilege of working independently and would love to bring my problem-solving, amongst many other skills to working in a team and providing help and assistance to customers/end-users.

### **Skills & Certifications**

Languages: JavaScript | Python

Frameworks: NodeJS | Python Flask | SQL | NoSQL

## **Work History**

#### **Hoop Telecoms**

Lagos, Nigeria

Jul. 2022 - May 2023

### Full Stack Web Developer (Intern - NYSC)

Singlehandedly developed and maintained customer information management system **Accomplishments**:

- Centralize customer info management; I integrated numerous customer data from across different spreadsheets used by different teams and departments to create a central system for managing customer data, improving customer service, and collaboration between different teams and departments.
- Appropriate access management to customer information; I utilized RBAC (Role Based Access Control) to give and restrict access to certain customer data based on employee's role and responsibilities, thereby boosting security and integrity over customer data.
- Centralizing access to core organizational data; as well as integrating customer data, I also integrated company data from different spreadsheets into this system reducing administrative cost as well as improving quality of work.

Tools used: Python Flask | REST API | SQL | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Git.

## **Notable Projects**

#### YelpCamp

Aug. 2023 - Nov. 2023

This project was done alongside the course instructor while learning NodeJs with Express.

- Implemented basic CRUD.
- Implemented tests with Postman.
- · Implemented RBAC.

Tools used: NodeJS | Postman | NoSQL | Git

https://yelp-camp-lrg5.onrender.com/

#### Trivia API

Aug. 2022 - Sept. 2022

This project was completed as a requirement during my Udacity Full Stack Developer Nanodegree course with Udacity.

- Designed API using RESTful principles.
- Implemented unit tests using Python's unittest module.
- Ensured it worked seamlessly with the React front end.

Tools used: Python Flask | REST API | SQL | Git

https://github.com/dee-obuaya/trivia-api-project.git

#### **Coffee Shop**

Sept. 2022 - Sept. 2022

This project was completed as a requirement during my Udacity Full Stack Developer Nanodegree course with Udacity.

- Designed API using RESTful principles.
- Implemented authentication and RBAC with Auth0.
- Implemented tests with Postman.
- Ensured it worked seamlessly with Ionic front end.

Tools used: Python Flask | REST API | SQL | Git | Postman | Auth0

https://github.com/dee-obuaya/coffee-shop.git

### **Education**

#### Udacity

**Full Stack Developer Nanodegree** 

Jul. 2022 – Nov. 2022

# University of Benin Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Benin City, Nigeria

Jan. 2018 – Sept. 2021

# International School Ibadan, University of Ibadan Cambridge A Level

Ibadan, Nigeria

Jan. 2016 - Nov. 2016